# Rebeka Farias

# **Full Stack Developer**

<u>rebekafarias.github.io/portfolio</u> • <u>linkedin.com/in/rebekafarias</u> • <u>github.com/rebekafarias</u> rebeka.farias@mackenzista.com.br • +55 11 9 7457-6451 • São Paulo, Brazil

### **Summary**

I have been a programmer for 4 years where I had experience with web development, process automation, APIs, data manipulation and UI design. I have mastery over languages such as **Python**, **JavaScript**, **Java** and **PHP**, always focusing on code quality.

#### Skills

Python • JavaScript • Java • PHP • Kotlin • Selenium • NodeJS • jQuery • Spring Boot • Laravel • Jetpack Compose • SQL • MySQL • SQLite • Git • Linux • SCRUM • KANBAN

### **Experience**

Systems Developer

## **Grupo SGCOR**

September 2023 - Present

API integration with PHP and Laravel, robotic process automation with Python and Selenium, web
development with JavaScript and jQuery.

Support Analyst

#### Ativa GR

February 2022 - May de 2023

• Ticket management with **Jira**, database maintenance with **MySQL**, web development with **Bootstrap**, automation with **C#** and **.NET**.

Intern

## **Class Solutions**

September 2021 - January 2022

• Development, maintenance and support for **SharePoint** sites using **PowerShell**.

#### Education

Bacharel em Análise e Desenvolvimento de Sistemas

**Universidade Presbiteriana Mackenzie** 

July 2021 - December 2023

Technical course of Systems Programmer for Mobile Devices

## Escola Técnica Estadual de São Paulo

May 2021 - October 2021

#### Languages

- Portuguese Native
- English Advanced

## Certificates

- Front End & UX/UI Design Origamid
- DevOps FIAP
- JavaScript Origamid
- Python FIAP
- Linux FIAP